

Profile

Software engineering student at Codam Coding College. I have a positive attitude, am prepared and driven to learn and master new skills. Exceptionally motivated to make a company thrive with all the experience I have gathered. I have a passion and big interest in game development.

Education

HAVO, St. Nicolaaslyceum, Amsterdam

SEPTEMBER 2013 - JUNE 2019

Graduated

Codam Coding College, Amsterdam

OCTOBER 2019 - PRESENT

Codam is a full time programming college in the heart of Amsterdam.

- Data structures, algorithms, multi-threading, unit-testing
- Programming in C
- Object-oriented programming in C++
- Linux, Bash, Git, Docker

Employment History

Sales, Gamma, Amsterdam

NOVEMBER 2016 - MAY 2017

Service, George Marina, Amsterdam

NOVEMBER 2017 - JULY 2021

Bartender, Brasserie Lolita, Amsterdam

JULY 2021 - PRESENT

College Projects

<u>cub3d</u>

Created a 3D looking game. Written in C with the use of **RayCasting**, inspired by the original Doom3D. Includes working with textures, levels, sprites, animations and complex mathematics.

• minishell

Created a replica of Bash that executes binaries using **multi-processing**. Written in C as a group project. Includes working with pipes and redirections.

• webserv

Created a fully functional webserver in C++98 using **sockets** to handle requests following the HTPP/1.1 protocol. Worked in a team of 3. Includes chuncking and fully functional python CGI.

• transcendence (in progress)

Creating a full stack app using **React**, **NestJS and Prisma** written in Typescript. Includes a pong replica to play multiplayer games, a fully functional chat with an admin panel, a friends list and an authentication system using OAuth. Worked in a team of 5.

For additional information regarding my projects, kindly refer to my <u>GitHub</u> profile.

Personal Details

Amstelvlietstraat 396 Amsterdam, 1096GG Netherlands +31 645264876 lukevincesmit@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Nederlands

DRIVING LICENSE

В

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

14-09-2000

Bussum

Links

Github

Linkedin

Codam

Skills

С

C++

TypeScript

Bash

Git

Docker

Mathematics

Problem-solving

Communication

Teamwork

Analytical

Languages

Dutch

English

Spanish

German